{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which continent has the largest population of elephants?",
      "correct": "Africa"
    },
    {
      "question": "Berlin, Paris and Madrid are capital cities in which continent?",
      "correct": "Europe"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which continent covers a third of the world's surface?",
      "correct": "Asia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which continent is the home of Elf, the world's smallest owl?",
      "correct": "NA"
    },
    {
      "question": "The smallest country in the world is in which continent?",
      "correct": "Europe"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which continent holds the largest country AND the most populated country?",
      "correct": "Asia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where would find the third longest river in the world, the Mississippi?",
      "correct": "NA"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which continent houses the world's largest coffee producing country?",
      "correct": "SA"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which continent is home to the Great Barrier Reef?",
      "correct": "Oceania"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which continent is the smallest by landmass?",
      "correct": "Oceania"
    },
    {
      "question": "Salar de Uyuni, the world's largest saltwater lake can be found in which continent?",
      "correct": "SA"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which continent is the source of 75% of the world's potatoes?",
      "correct": "Europe"
    },
    {
      "question": "66% of all the world's chocolate comes from which continent?",
      "correct": "Africa"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which continent is the largest by landmass and population?",
      "correct": "Asia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which continent has the smallest population of just 1,106 residents?",
      "correct": "Antarctica"
    }
  ]
}
